

#### **ABOUT ME**

I work as a freelance front end developer and I am an academic tutor of a web development course at Coder House. I have worked in large companies for 10 years building different skills such as teamwork and good work communication. I also have a degree in nutrition, which allows me to have a different vision when working in computer science. I would like to work in a company where I can apply my skills and knowledge to improve the value of the final product.

### **EDUCATION**

FRONT END DEVELOPER CAREER -2021

CODER HOUSE|graduated

**NUTRITIONIST** - 2019 UNIVERSIDAD ABIERTA INTERAMERICANA| graduated

# **LENGUAGES**

Spanish native English advanced (FCE)

# **GIT HUB REPOSITORY**

github.com/AnaliaMancuso

### LINKEDIN

linkedin.com/in/analia-mancuso-negreira/

#### PERSONAL INFORMATION

Phone number: +54 9 11 6687 0711

• E-mail: analiamancusoelive.com

• Date of birth: February 27, 1991

• Nacionality: Argentina

• Location: Buenos Aires, Argentina

# ANALIA MANCUSO NEGREIRA

# FRONT END DEVELOPER

#### **EXPERIENCE**

#### FRONT END DEVELOPER

#### Freelance-October 2020-present

- Structuring and development of current and attractive websites.
- Ranking of relevant content
- Positioning of the website in search engines.
- Reading adaptability, functionality and dynamism to all screen sizes
- Configuration of contact feedback with potential clients
- Animations and calls to action on the site

# WEB DEVELOPMENT COURSE ACADEMIC TUTOR Coder House- June 2021-present

- Practical work tutoring
- Support for students to solve problems
- Response to code queries

## **SKILLS**

- Web layout HTML 5
- Javascript
- jQuery
- React is
- CSS 3 and SCSS
- JSON, API
- Bootstrap, Materialize, Material UI
- Whimsical, Balsamiq
- Git and GitHub repositories
- Hosting
- SEO optimization
- Jira
- Agile work technologies
- PWA optimization
- Advanced office package advanced: Excel,
   Word, Access, Power Point and Photoshop UTN

#### **OTHER EXPERIENCES**

#### **NUTRITIONIST**

#### Independent- March 2020-present

- Attention to patients with various pathologies such as obesity, dyslipidemia, metabolic syndrome and hepatitis, as well as those with varied eating patterns from ovo-lactovegetarianism, plant based diet to veganism.
- Prescription of meal plans adapted to the present pathologies and / or to the chosen feeding pattern to cover the nutritional requirements corresponding to each case.
- Food education including culinary techniques, choice of products in the market and batch cooking.

#### **NUTRITIONIST**

# Francisco J. Muñiz Infectious Diseases Hospital- April 2019 - August 2019

- Nutritional evaluation of patients, including ICU, patients with tuberculosis, HIV, liver disease and pediatrics using Subjective Global Assessment, adapted for patients with liver cirrhosis, and adapted to HIV patients, The Royal Free Hospital Nutritional Prioritizing Tool (RFH-NPT), Nutritional Risk Screening (NRS 2002) and Objective Global Assessment (VGO).
- Prescription of meal plans adapted to hospitalized and discharge patients.
- Nutrition education for patients and their families.

#### **NUTRITIONIST**

#### CAPS "El Encuentro" Febrary 2019- April 2019

- Nutritional care in the community patients' office.
- Anthropometric evaluation of patients, food anamnesis, food education, prescription of food plans adapted to the pathology or health situation such as obesity, arterial hypertension, metabolic syndrome, pregnancy and pediatrics.
- Control and monitoring of cases.

#### **RECEPTIONIST**

#### **Grupo Insud- August 2014-present**

- Reception of visits.
- Magnetic card loading and configuration (Win Pak system). Switch handling.
- Registration and preparation of Excel spreadsheets and graphics. Courier delivery.
   Reception and delivery of correspondence.
- Coordination of meeting rooms. Assistance to CEO for vacation coverage of his secretary: flight coordination, hotel reservation, meetings.

#### **RECEPTIONIST**

# Perez Alati, Grondona, Benites & Arntsen-March 2013- April 2014

- Reception of visits.
- Coordination of meeting rooms.

# ADMINISTRATIVE EMPLOYEE Lomas Athletic Club- January 2009 December 2012

- Administrative Tasks (Preparation and loading of accounting entries, Bank reconciliations).
- Requests for budgets and supplies, invoice control and their transfer to the current account system